Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪In the old house, a light breeze blows♪
♪في البيت القديم، تهب نسمة خفيفة♪
♪Carrying a wisp of floral fragrance♪
♪تحمل خصلة من العطر الزهري♪
♪You left in such haste, without hesitation♪
♪لقد غادرت على عجل، دون تردد♪
♪Before I could even feel the joy♪
♪قبل أن أشعر بالفرح♪
♪I dared not write a single word♪
♪لم أجرؤ على كتابة كلمة واحدة♪
♪Afraid it would give my heart away♪
♪أخشى أن يكشف قلبي♪
♪Leaving behind a foolish soul in loneliness♪
♪ترك وراءه روحًا حمقاء في الوحدة♪
♪The world grows old♪
♪العالم يشيخ♪
♪Time slips by like a blade♪
♪يمر الوقت مثل الشفرة♪
♪Through every day and night as I wait for the flowers to bloom♪
♪في كل يوم وليلة وأنا أنتظر الزهور لتتفتح♪
♪It feels as though a thousand years never passed♪
♪أشعر وكأن ألف عام لم تمر أبدًا♪
♪The wind lets petals fall into your palm♪
♪الريح تجعل البتلات تسقط في راحة يدك♪
♪Love makes us foolish, lost in endless memories♪
♪الحب يجعلنا حمقى، ضائعين في ذكريات لا نهاية لها♪
♪No one cares about our story♪
♪لا أحد يهتم بقصتنا♪
♪Slowly fading away♪
♪تتلاشى ببطء♪
♪Flowers bloom in snow, brief as life itself♪
♪تزهر الزهور في الثلج، قصيرة مثل الحياة نفسها♪
♪So many poems through the ages speak of♪
♪تتحدث العديد من القصائد عبر العصور عن♪
♪Love and hatred, partings and vows of the past♪
♪الحب والكراهية، الفراق وعهود الماضي♪
♪Had we never crossed paths in this lifetime♪
♪لو لم نلتقي قط في هذه الحياة♪
♪Nothing could separate us, even if we were oceans apart♪
♪لا شيء يمكن أن يفصلنا، حتى لو كنا بعيدين عن بعضنا البعض بالمحيطات♪
=The Princess Decree=
=مرسوم الأميرة=
=Episode 18=
=الحلقة 18=
(Princess Royal Yong'an's Residence)
(مقر إقامة الأميرة الملكية يونغآن)
I, Official Li Yuanze, request an audience with the Princess Royal.
أنا، المسؤول لي يوانزي، أطلب مقابلة مع الأميرة الملكية.
with the Princess Royal!
مع الأميرة الملكية!
Xing, please inform Her Highness that I have urgent matters to report.
شينغ، يرجى إبلاغ صاحبة السمو بأن لدي أمورًا عاجلة يجب الإبلاغ عنها.
Official Li, please leave.
السيد الرسمي لي، يرجى المغادرة.
Her Highness said there is no need to see you again.
وقالت صاحبة السمو أنه ليس هناك حاجة لرؤيتك مرة أخرى.
If that is so,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
I will wait here until Her Highness agrees to see me.
سأنتظر هنا حتى توافق صاحبة السمو على رؤيتي.
I, Official Li Yuanze,
أنا، المسؤول لي يوانزي،
request an audience with the Princess Royal.
اطلب مقابلة مع الأميرة الملكية.
I, Official Li Yuanze,
أنا، المسؤول لي يوانزي،
request an audience with the Princess Royal!
اطلب مقابلة مع الأميرة الملكية!
I, Official Li Yuanze,
أنا، المسؤول لي يوانزي،
request an audience with the Princess Royal!
اطلب مقابلة مع الأميرة الملكية!
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Official Li refuses to leave.
المسؤول لي يرفض المغادرة.
He said he will wait forever if he must.
قال أنه سوف ينتظر إلى الأبد إذا كان لا بد من ذلك.
I, Official Li Yuanze,
أنا، المسؤول لي يوانزي،
request an audience with the Princess Royal!
اطلب مقابلة مع الأميرة الملكية!
I, Official Li Yuanze,
أنا، المسؤول لي يوانزي،
request an audience with the Princess Royal.
اطلب مقابلة مع الأميرة الملكية.
(Qingya and White Deer)
(تشينغيا والغزال الأبيض)
I, Official Li Yuanze,
أنا، المسؤول لي يوانزي،
request an audience with the Princess Royal!
اطلب مقابلة مع الأميرة الملكية!
(Princess Royal Yong'an's Residence)
(مقر إقامة الأميرة الملكية يونغآن)
Enough.
كافٍ.
Let him in.
دعوه يدخل.
Yes.
نعم.
Official Li, please.
المسؤول لي من فضلك.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Sit.
يجلس.
It is bitterly cold outside.
إنه بارد جدا في الخارج.
I should have invited you in sooner.
كان ينبغي لي أن أدعوك في وقت سابق.
But whenever I recall the past,
ولكن كلما تذكرت الماضي،
I cannot help wanting you to endure more of the wind and snow.
لا أستطيع إلا أن أتمنى لك أن تتحمل المزيد من الرياح والثلوج.
Yet on second thought,
ولكن بعد تفكير ثانٍ،
what is past
ما هو الماضي
should remain in the past.
ينبغي أن تبقى في الماضي.
Holding onto it
التمسك بها
is meaningless in the end.
ليس له معنى في النهاية.
It holds meaning.
فهو يحمل معنى.
A debt is still a debt.
الدين يبقى دينًا.
It cannot be erased.
لا يمكن مسحه.
This is what I owe Your Highness,
هذا ما أدين به لسموك،
and I should repay it.
ويجب علي أن أسددها.
Your Highness, do you know
صاحب السمو هل تعلم
what was on my mind
ما كان في ذهني
while I waited outside?
بينما كنت أنتظر في الخارج؟
I wondered
لقد تساءلت
whether the snow five years ago
هل كان الثلج قبل خمس سنوات
was just as heavy as today.
كان ثقيلاً تماماً كما هو اليوم.
You treated me
لقد عاملتني
far better than I treated you.
أفضل بكثير من تعاملي معك.
Back then,
في ذلك الوقت،
I did not even offer you
ولم اقدم لك حتى
a cup of warm tea.
كوب من الشاي الدافئ.
Did you come today,
هل أتيت اليوم؟
simply to reminisce with me?
فقط للتذكر معي؟
But
لكن
we no longer have a reason
لم يعد لدينا سبب
to meet like this.
للقاء مثل هذا.
No.
لا.
I came today with urgent matters to report.
لقد جئت اليوم لأخبرك بأمور عاجلة.
Please look, Your Highness.
من فضلك أنظر يا صاحب السمو.
Using the excuse of leaving the capital,
بحجة مغادرة العاصمة،
Gan Sheng sent a cavalry unit directly to the mines.
أرسل جان شنغ وحدة من سلاح الفرسان مباشرة إلى المناجم.
I suspect that he is
أظن أنه هو
- manufacturing weapons in secret. - Manufacturing weapons in secret.
- تصنيع الأسلحة سراً.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
Gan Sheng harbors treasonous intent.
يبدو أن جان شنغ يحمل نوايا خيانية.
I understand.
أفهم.
This matter,
هذا الأمر،
I will handle myself.
سأتعامل مع الأمر بنفسي.
Official Li.
لي الرسمي.
Please leave.
من فضلك أرحل.
Your Highness, I still have urgent...
صاحب السمو، لا يزال لدي أمر عاجل...
Official Li.
لي الرسمي.
Thank you for telling me truthfully.
شكرا لك على قولك لي الحقيقة.
But I
ولكن انا
no longer have anything
لم يعد لدي أي شيء
left to trade with you.
غادر للتجارة معك.
Your Highness has already done more than enough.
لقد فعلت سموكم ما يكفي بالفعل.
Since returning to the capital,
منذ العودة إلى العاصمة،
you have been restraining Gan Sheng from the shadows.
لقد قمت بمنع جان شنغ من الظلال.
You stepped into the game yourself
لقد دخلت اللعبة بنفسك
and bought precious time for His Majesty.
وكسبت وقتا ثمينا لجلالته.
You even acted first
حتى أنك تصرفت أولاً
and saved Mrs. Liu and Zhao from him.
وأنقذ السيدة ليو وتشاو منه.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
under the guise of humiliating me,
تحت ستار إهانتي،
you were testing the scholars,
كنت تختبر العلماء،
and preserved the upright officials of court.
وحفظ رجال القضاء المستقيمين.
You even exposed disgrace like Vice Minister Wang.
حتى أنك كشفت العار مثل نائب الوزير وانغ.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
that day in the prison,
ذلك اليوم في السجن،
you went to kill him as well,
لقد ذهبت لقتله أيضًا
right?
يمين؟
In the past, I understood very little.
في الماضي، لم أفهم إلا القليل.
Now I understand everything.
الآن فهمت كل شيء.
Li Yuanze,
لي يوانزي,
what is it that you truly want?
ما هو الذي تريده حقا؟
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
Gan Sheng is wildly ambitious.
جان شنغ طموح للغاية.
If we continue to fight separately,
إذا واصلنا القتال بشكل منفصل،
I fear it will be difficult to stop his schemes.
أخشى أن يكون من الصعب إيقاف مخططاته.
Right now danger is pressing upon us.
في هذه اللحظة الخطر يضغط علينا.
It is a moment of life and death.
إنها لحظة حياة وموت.
I am
أنا أكون
willing to stand with Your Highness.
على استعداد للوقوف مع سموكم.
Let us protect Jing together.
دعونا نحمي جينغ معًا.
I hope Your Highness will grant this.
آمل أن يمنحك سموكم هذا.
Li Yuanze.
لي يوانزي.
Give me your hand.
أعطني يدك.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Remember this.
تذكر هذا.
Xiao Pingning and Li Yuanze share no bond.
لا يوجد أي رابط بين Xiao Pingning و Li Yuanze .
From this day forward, those who walk side by side
من هذا اليوم فصاعدا، أولئك الذين يسيرون جنبًا إلى جنب
are the Princess Royal of Jing and the Grand Secretary.
هما الأميرة الملكية لجينغ والأمين العام.
♪When we first met, moonlight rippled on the water♪
♪عندما التقينا لأول مرة، كان ضوء القمر يتلألأ على الماء♪
♪Your silhouette in dreams turning back with gentle eyes♪
♪ظلك في الأحلام تعود بعيون لطيفة♪
♪A trace upon my heart, a thought quietly hidden♪
♪أثر على قلبي، فكرة مخفية بهدوء♪
♪Words almost spoken, yet our story froze in time♪
♪الكلمات كادت أن تُقال، لكن قصتنا تجمدت في الزمن♪
♪Your gaze felt familiar♪
♪نظرتك كانت مألوفة♪
♪Etched into my heart, one tear swelling into a sea♪
♪محفورة في قلبي، دمعة واحدة تتضخم في البحر♪
♪How many times have we brushed past as our fates wavered?♪
♪كم مرة مررنا بمصيرنا عندما ترددت أقدارنا؟♪
♪Only to circle back into someone's open palm♪
♪فقط للعودة إلى راحة يد شخص ما المفتوحة♪
♪That moment I saw you, spring awakened in me♪
♪في تلك اللحظة التي رأيتك فيها، أيقظ الربيع في داخلي♪
♪My heart suddenly becomes soft and tender♪
♪قلبي فجأة يصبح رقيقًا وحنونًا♪
♪Longing flowed and stirring waves of affection♪
♪تدفق الشوق وحرك أمواج المودة♪
♪Smiles and tears blurred everything in the past♪
♪الابتسامات والدموع طمس كل شيء في الماضي♪
♪The words were similar♪
♪الكلمات كانت متشابهة♪
♪With eyes closed, it felt like you were right beside me♪
♪مع عيون مغلقة، شعرت وكأنك كنت بجانبي مباشرة♪
♪That moment I saw you, spring awakened in me♪
♪في تلك اللحظة التي رأيتك فيها، أيقظ الربيع في داخلي♪
♪My heart suddenly becomes soft and tender♪
♪قلبي فجأة يصبح رقيقًا وحنونًا♪
♪Longing flowed and stirring waves of affection♪
♪تدفق الشوق وحرك أمواج المودة♪
♪Smiles and tears blurred everything in the past♪
♪الابتسامات والدموع طمس كل شيء في الماضي♪
♪The words were similar♪
♪الكلمات كانت متشابهة♪
♪With eyes closed, it felt like you were right beside me♪
♪مع عيون مغلقة، شعرت وكأنك كنت بجانبي مباشرة♪
♪After we part and meet again♪
♪بعد أن نفترق ونلتقي مرة أخرى♪
♪Your face had already changed♪
♪وجهك قد تغير بالفعل♪
♪Longing flowed and stirring waves of affection♪
♪تدفق الشوق وحرك أمواج المودة♪
♪If your words are clear♪
♪إذا كانت كلماتك واضحة♪
♪Like an image carved in the bones♪
♪مثل صورة منحوتة في العظام♪
♪It doesn't matter whose skin the soul hides underneath♪
♪لا يهم من يختبئ تحت جلد الروح♪